<blog>
    <item>
        <title>SN9</title>
        <date>February 4, 2021</date>
        <text>
            If you are here and haven't seen SN9, go watch it. Seriously. Big boom. Spacex is always doing cool shit. Hire me Elon...
        </text>
        <image>/assets/blog/sn9.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Coding</title>
        <date>February 4, 2021</date>
        <text>
            I have been working a lot on coding skills the last while, check out my github. Did some AI, datastructures and algorithm stuff, and its all pretty cool
        </text>
        <image>/assets/blog/github.png</image>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Time</title>
        <date>December 30, 2020</date>
        <text>
            Clocks cannot tell our time of day ~~
            For what event to pray~~
            Because we have no time, because ~~
            We have no time until~~
            We know what time we fill~~
            Why time is other than time was.
        </text>
        <image>/assets/blog/clock.png</image>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Blender</title>
        <date>December 19, 2020</date>
        <text>
            Blender: ~~~~
            I hate you and I'll see you tomorrow :/
            (im in love)
        </text>
        <image>/assets/blog/blender.png</image>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Bellyflop</title>
        <date>December 13, 2020</date>
        <text>
            Rocket go up. ~~
            Rocket go bellyflop. ~~
            Rocket go down. ~~
            Rocket go boom. :( ~~~~
            Lack of propellent do be like dat doe
            https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qraeGw0kn7o
        </text>
        <image>/assets/blog/sn8.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Website Updates</title>
        <date>November 29, 2020</date>
        <text>
            So been working on my website this weekend and just pushed this to my website. It all looks pretty good :)
            ~~~~
            The homepage might need some work, but that's a problem for another time. My website is now more Javascript than anything else according to Github,
            which is what I was going for as I wanted the most of it to be really easy to edit with XML files and all the HTML be handled by JS.
        </text>
        <image>/assets/blog/github.png</image>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Rocket</title>
        <date>November 26, 2020</date>
        <text>Just finished up with my model rocket, the files are all on my github and I am SUPER PUMPED to launch it this week. The nosecone is just finishing up on the printer,
        so I just have to build the launchpad and install the engine.</text>
        <image>/assets/blog/sn9.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Ender 3 Pro</title>
        <date>November 24, 2020</date>
        <text>I've been messing around with my printer the last few days, and have made a lot of progress. It took about 10 hours to build and level the bed, 
        but now I've got it going really smoothly and have been running prints non-stop that I have been planning for the last while. Most of those files are 
        on my github.</text>
        <image>/assets/blog/ender3.png</image>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Funeral Music</title>
        <date>November 21, 2020</date>
        <text>PLEASE PLAY THIS SONG WHEN I DIE. Home - We're finally landing. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zR6fECxF44I</text>
        <image>/assets/blog/home.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>3D Printer</title>
        <date>November 20, 2020</date>
        <text>MY ENDER 3 IS COMING THIS WEEKEND!!!!!! Shoutout to Tyler for agreeing to put up with me and help build it.
        The man is a freaking genius.</text>
        <image>/assets/blog/ender3.png</image>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Model Rocket</title>
        <date>November 20, 2020</date>
        <text>Well. I'm printing my first model of the rocket I'm building. My tech design teacher let me use his printer, so
        I'm excited to launch that soon. I'm going to try launching it with an A class engine, just to see the height, and then
        I may go out and get a C class engine depending on how high it goes off the bat. My friend is giving me a few rocket engines
        to mess around with and text. Hopefully I can have it in the air by next week.</text>
        <image>/assets/blog/sn9.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Websites</title>
        <date>November 19, 2020</date>
        <text>Websites. So rewarding. And a pain in the ass. I have probably spent 40 hours on my website version 3,
        and i just decided I really don't like it. Look at it. It's ugly. So I am resorting to a similar layout of
        my website version 2. Hopefully I can take everything I've learned and use it to make this one actually good.</text>
        <image>/assets/blog/github.png</image>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Blog</title>
        <date>November 19, 2020</date>
        <text>So I guess this is my blog... welcome. (PS, hover to see the full blog content when its too big to view.)</text>
        <image>/assets/blog/blog-art.jpg</image>
    </item>
</blog>